<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on RISCV ISA extensions Ghidra field guide</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/riscv_vector_survey/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on RISCV ISA extensions Ghidra field guide</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/riscv_vector_survey/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Glossary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/riscv_vector_survey/docs/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/riscv_vector_survey/docs/glossary/</guid>
      <description>Vector terms Detailed Reference&#xA;Acronyms AVL Application Vector Length, the total number of elements to be processed as a candidate value for vl EEW Each vector operand has an effective element width (EEW) and an effective LMUL (EMUL) that is used to determine the size and location of all the elements within a vector register group. By default, for most operands of most instructions, EEW=SEW and EMUL=LMUL. ELEN The maximum size in bits of a vector element that any operation can produce or consume, ELEN ≥ 8, which must be a power of 2.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISCV-64 toolchain and deployment environment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/riscv_vector_survey/docs/testbed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/riscv_vector_survey/docs/testbed/</guid>
      <description>We use two RISCV-64 applications to examine the impact of extensions to the RISCV-64 Instruction Set Architecture. These are:&#xA;dpdk-ip_pipeline - a network application framework example where one wouldn&amp;rsquo;t expect a lot of vector math. whisper.cpp - a Inference Engine voice-to-text application which uses a lot of tensor math We use the latest RISCV toolchains available to understand what the newer toolchains may soon mean to Ghidra analyses. At present that means a GCC 15 compiler and binutils assembler close to the development tip.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
